That will switch between "esque", what kind of horoscope features usually have contains
and to put them in separate top-ground stench them, just so you start it.
We see like a time-based horoscope, but the gory is specific, it has such a priority
tabs quickly.
Okay, plan it for me and implement to the current design.
These keep colors similar, please keep the design to attachment.
And as a previous stage, I have this star-crossed extension that is here.
Now we still get some sort of tool, because it's a polybic, but we can try to use like
the soulmate.
And then I can put it here, so it's soulmate so they're short.
And now I will press and attach it and it will now prepare next moves to create this
extension.
Okay, now I can press "view plan", yeah we have the implementation details, the structure,
the vidoscript functionality for an ordinary birthday and stunning that we obviously take
an expression for that, now I press "view" and let's wait for the result.
Let me reload the extension, now to see the result, I see the star-crossed, but what I'm
only trusting is just to see the managed extension, I will load it in the pack, I'll
go to the cross-coruscov new tab.
And now I can open a new tab, it obviously is a kippet, and we have our daily horoscope.
As you can see, it's changing, now I can change some compatibility between signs, 90%,
and there is even a calculator for soulmate, so if you pass like some random type and use
this like this, and maybe, like this, the birth time can be in the birth location with
the city and country, so the first one will be England, Sweden, I'll show it to you,
Cocoa, but it's showing some signs, so there is some algorithm behind that, and here
we have even some sub-exign, so if you will type your time, and now we can type birth
site, I will spoil it, you can calculate, and we have some of the designs, great, but I think
to extend it more, it would be better if it won't, some of the application, and manually take
a screenshot, and then step-by-step implemented in there.
Crown cursor, as you can see, we have a pretty good foundation to extend it and create
more of functionalities later on.